http://www.advancedlabelsnw.com/privacy?hsLang=en

Application
F.A.Q.
Privacy Policy
At Advanced Labels we respect your privacy, and the private information that you may provide us as a user of this website. We do not require your personal information to access this site. However, you may choose to supply information about yourself to obtain certain services or content provided by our company. Rest assured that any personal information that you supply to us is safeguarded and honored.
Information Collected:
The personal information that you provide such as names, email addresses, postal addresses, phone numbers, etc., is entered into our database of prospective customers. By viewing our site, Advanced Labels may also collect certain statistical data about your visit to our website including pages visited, amount of time spent at the site, IP address, browser type, ISP information, your operating system and other data for use in website administration.
Information Usage:
Any information that you provide us is collected into our database and used to deliver services such as requests for quotes, label samples, customer surveys and internal order processing. We may also use the information to provide you with special offers or updates of new products that might be of interest to you. None of your information will ever be sold, rented or in any way shared with another party. However, as authorized or required by law we may share your information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting in investigations.
Opt-Out:
On occasion we will promote special offers and discounts via postal service mailings or email campaigns to our customers/prospects via our database. These mailings are rather infrequent, typically one per quarter. You have the choice to not receive these or additional emails by selecting the corresponding box for Special Offer Notification when entering in your personal information. Alternatively you can contact our customer service staff directly to request removal from our mailing list by sending an email.
Third Party Links:
This site may contain links to other sites which are out of the control of Advanced Labels. We do not monitor the privacy policies of those sites. Please consult the respective sites privacy policies for details on their practices.
Contact Information:
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please feel free to contact a customer service representative: 1-800-877-4312.
Be Social:
Copyright © 2018  Advanced Labels NW \\ A Resource Label Group Co.
Phone: (425) 776-4315 \\ Toll Free: (800) 877-4312
Privacy Policy | Site Map | Terms and Conditions
